Hi, Mr. Xu.
许力哥
Mr. Ji
纪总说
asked me to work under you.
让我先跟着您
I would
之后就
appreciate your guidance.
多多指教
Oh, cool.
好
Then, um,
那 那个
if you have any questions,
以后你有什么不懂的事
feel free to ask me.
随时来问我
Alright.
好
So,
那现在
is there anything I can do?
我有什么可以做的吗
I'm new, I'm eager to learn.
我刚来想多学习
One sec.
等一下啊
Let me see.
我看看
Well,
行
you can take these
那你先拿这几本
and read them.
回去看一下
I'm always here
有什么不懂的
for your questions.
随时过来问我
OK.
好
I need to go to HR now.
但我得先去趟人事
I'll be back later.
我待会儿回来
Alright.
好
In your face.
谢谢你的秤
Xiaoning.
筱柠
Hey.
姐
We're colleagues again.
真巧又成同事了
It is quite a coincidence.
是挺巧的
I didn't expect you
我也没想到
to come to our dept.
你会来拓展部
Because there are some
因为有一些
very important issues
很重要的事情
that I need to finish in here.
我要在这里完成
By the way,
对了
I heard that
听说
you and Yuheng
你跟我师哥
are high school alumni.
也是高中校友
Are you close?
你们熟吗
We are alumni.
是校友
Same grade,
同级
but not in the same class.
但不在一个班
Not very close.
不是很熟
That's good.
那还挺好的
Otherwise, like me,
要不然像我似的
I have to act distant with him
还得跟师哥
to avoid suspicion.
装生疏避嫌
It's quite bothering.
怪麻烦的
By the way,
对了筱柠姐
for our office supplies and
我们这些员工的
the name tag,
办公用品还有工牌
are you the one who collects them?
是不是都你领啊
Please get me a set too.
帮我也领一份
Why?
为什么
Back when we're working in the lobby,
之前在大堂的时候
it was
就是
the ones on probation
一些没有转正的员工
running such stuff.
做这些事情
But now,
现在
we're working for the BDD.
是在拓展部
I'm an assistant to account managers,
我是客户经理助理
and so are you.
你也是
Got it.
好
Xiaoning,
小涂
try these plums
尝尝
I just bought.
新买的话梅
Feels like you're trying to
无事献殷勤的感觉
curry favor.
小赵哥
You
你
don't get along with Yuhui, right?
跟小唐不对付啊
We are fine.
没有什么对付不对付的
This is actually yummy.
挺好吃的
I'd like to buy dinner tonight.
第一天想请大家吃顿饭
I've reserved a private room at Juchuan.
我在菊川订了包间
Please come and join me.
希望各位哥哥姐姐
It would mean a lot to me!
赏脸光临
Yuhui's got to have connections
这领导跟小唐的关系
with our boss.
不一般啊
Sure, smart guy.
你又知道
You seem to know everything.
小赵哥你什么都知道
We'll head over now.
我们先过去了
Alright, see you.
好 拜拜
See you.
拜拜
Take care, bye.
慢点啊 拜拜
See you later.
一会见
Yuhui,
小唐
can you give me a ride later?
一会儿捎我一段呗
Xu Li, I'm kind of occupied now.
许力哥我还有点事
You guys go ahead.
你们要不先过去
I'll catch up soon.
我待会儿马上就到
Alright, no worries.
好 好没事
Ms. Rao,
静姐
Mr. Zhao and I
那个我跟小赵哥
didn't drive today.
今天都没开车
Can we carpool with you?
蹭你个车呗
Sorry,
不好意思啊
I only let cute young guys
姐的副驾驶呢
sit in my passenger seat.
只坐年轻的小弟弟
You'll have to figure it out on your own.
自己想办法吧啊
Xiaoning,
小涂
follow me.
跟我走
Go!
走
Rely on yourself rather than others.
求人不如求己
Let's take the subway.
坐地铁
Sounds good.
好
Wait for me.
等我一会儿哥
No.
不等
What's up, Yuhui?
怎么了小唐
Yuheng.
师哥
We are off.
下班了
They're heading to Juchuan.
他们都去了菊川
Let's head out too.
我们也走吧
They've already left?
他们已经去了
I was specifically waiting for you.
我特意等你下班的
OK.
好
By the way, Yuhui.
对了小唐
From now on,
以后在单位
just call me Mr. Ji at work.
还是叫我纪总好
OK.
好
Are you disinfecting the dishes?
消毒啊
Maybe I should disinfect you?
要不给你消消毒
It's getting late.
这都几点了
Why haven't Mr. Ji and
这老大和唐羽卉
Tang Yuhui arrived yet?
怎么还不来啊
Senior, junior,
师哥 师妹
a perfect pair.
成双成对呗
They must be arriving together.
他俩肯定一块来
Is this the right place?
是这吧
Yes, right.
就是这儿
Sorry.
抱歉
Sorry, everyone.
抱歉 各位
The traffic was terrible.
路上太堵了
We're late.
我们来晚了
I'll sit here.
我坐这儿吧
Then I'll sit over there.
那我坐那边
Yuhui,
小唐
how about we switch seats?
咱俩换一下吧
This spot is right by the air vent.
这儿是出风口
I'm a bit under the weather.
我这两天有点感冒
Here.
来
Alright.
好
Mr. Zhao, come here.
哥你坐这边
So,
那
Yuheng,
师哥
everyone's here, shall we go?
人都来齐了咱们开始吗
Sure, just do it.
大家动筷吧
You go first.
你来
Xiaoning has always been my senior.
筱柠姐一直都是我前辈
Please.
姐你先来
Thanks.
好啊
Well, then,
这样吧
I'd like to
我先
propose a toast to all.
敬大家一个
Back
各位
when I was working in the lobby,
之前呢在大堂
I achieved
我虽然稍微有那么
some minor results,
一点点成绩
but in section one,
但是到了拓展部
I'm still a rookie.
我还是新人
So,
之后呢还希望
please
各位前辈们
look out for me.
能多多照顾
If you ever need anything from me,
之后有需要我的地方
just let me know.
尽管提
Here's to everyone!
敬各位
You and Mr. Ji
放心吧
came from the same uni,
纪总的学妹
we'll definitely take care of you.
我们一定是要照顾的
Actually, regarding Qingbei graduates,
其实我们清北同系的
most of us are finance majors.
大部分都在 金融系
In the finance industry,
那在金融行业
speaking of Dairui,
说到我们代瑞
there are about seven or eight
有七八个师弟和师妹
graduates after me working here.
都在我们这儿
Xu Li,
许力呀
how about
要不你都
looking out for them all?
照顾 照顾
Mr. Ji is absolutely right.
纪总说得对
It's not fair to give Yuhui
你不能因为小唐
preferential treatment
是纪总的师妹
just for her relations with Mr. Ji.
就对人家多多照顾
It's a sign of disrespect for the skills
你这是看低了
of graduates from an elite uni.
人家名牌大学的能力
Besides,
再说了
no one makes it into section one
能进我们拓展一部的
through connections.
哪个靠的是裙带关系
Absolutely!
是 是 是
My bad!
怪我 怪我
Well,
那个
I'll take a drink as punishment.
我自罚一杯
Xu Li, you're such a drinker.
许力你那么能喝
Is one drink enough?
罚一杯够吗
Make it a whole bottle.
罚一壶
Sounds good!
行啊
Mr. Zhao
那哥
you've got to join me.
那你陪一个
Yuheng, please try this.
师哥你尝尝这个
It's just-caught.
这个特别新鲜
I specifically ordered it.
我专门要的
OK, thanks.
好 谢谢
By the way, Xiaoning,
对了小涂
I noticed that the doctor from Renji
我看仁济医院那个医生
hasn't been around lately.
最近好像没来找你了
Are you two completely over?
你俩是不是彻底没戏了
It's OK.
没关系
How about this.
这样吧
Just tell me
你跟小赵哥说说
what your ideal type is.
你的理想型是什么
I happen to know a few
我这边正好有几个
really good guys.
不错的优质男青年
Ideal type, huh?
理想型啊
I'm into artsy types.
文艺男青年
As for looks,
长得
that's not a big deal.
倒是无所谓
I like shoulder-length hair.
长发披肩的
What's important is that he keeps
重点是要懂得跟异性
a respectful distance from women.
保持距离
Maintain clear boundaries.
有恰到好处的边界感
I've got one.
有
My classmate's brother
我一同学弟弟
fits that bill.
就是这类型
Next week,
下周
I'll ask him out,
我把他约出来
so you two can meet
你俩见面
and have a chat.
好好聊一聊
What do you think?
怎么样
A blind date?
相亲啊
Sounds great!
好啊
Thanks, Mr. Zhao.
谢谢小赵哥
It's a plan then.
那就这么定了
Are you alright?
师哥没事吧
Thanks.
谢谢
Yuheng,
师哥
are you...
你这是
What's your ideal type like?
你的理想型啥样啊
Screw you.
滚
Yuhui.
小唐
Here, here.
来 来 来
Take it easy, Li.
哥你少喝点
Alright, alright.
好 好 好
I'm not great with alcohol.
我酒量不好
This place you chose is fantastic.
特好吃今天这地儿选的
Good, huh?
好吃是吧
So good.
好吃 好吃
I specially made a reservation in here.
我专门定的
It's really good.
特别好吃
Should I order some more?
那我再加点
We need to talk.
你出来一趟
Good.
好啊
- Yuhui. - Ms. Rao.
小唐 静姐
- I'm going to the restroom. - Come on.
我去个洗手间 来
Let's have a drink.
咱们也喝一个
Don't be afraid of any difficulties.
以后有什么困难
- OK. - I'm at your disposal.
好 你跟我说啊
I'll definitely help
我能帮上的
if I can.
我肯定会帮到
Thanks.
哥你多照顾
No problem.
没问题
Bottoms up!
干了
Were you being serious?
刚刚是认真的吗
What do you mean?
什么
About your ideal type.
你的理想型标准啊
Were you being serious?
是认真的吗
Doesn't everyone
每个人
have an ideal type?
不都有理想型吗
What?
怎么了
Can't I have one?
我不能有啊
So you're going on a blind date?
所以就去相亲
Is that the reason
你就因为这个事
you called me out?
叫我出来的
Let go of me.
你先把我放开
Mr. Zhao is a man of pride.
小赵哥好面子吗
With so many people around,
那么多人在那儿
I shouldn't embarrass him.
我不好驳他面子的
Later on,
回头
I'll find a way to turn it down.
找个机会拒绝就好了
No need to wait or
不用回头
look for an opportunity.
也不用再找机会
After dinner,
结束以后
just tell him.
告诉他
This is my own business.
这是我自己的事
I'll handle it myself.
我会处理好的
Yuheng.
师哥
are you in there?
你在里面吗
Mr. Ji,
纪总
you should really focus on
你还是好好处理处理
your own issues.
自己的事情吧
Your sweet junior is looking for you.
你小师妹来找你了
How come
师哥你怎么
you came out from there?
从那边出来了
I accidentally went to the wrong one.
找错房间了
Let's go.
走吧
Yuheng,
师哥
back on campus, you mentioned
你在学校的时候
you liked girls with high ponytails.
说喜欢高马尾的女孩
What about now?
现在呢
Ms. Rao, Ms. Rao!
静姐 静姐
Um,
那个
Xiang and I
我跟想我俩
are going for another around.
下一场
Mr. Zhao didn't drive here.
赵哥没开车
Could you please give him a ride?
麻烦您送他一下啊
Me?
我送啊
Yeah, yeah.
对 对 对
Actually, I can't.
我送不了
Listen up, my car
我跟你讲我的车
only accommodates good-looking guys.
只坐帅哥啊
You take him home.
你给他送回去
Take him home, take him home.
送回去 送回去
Let's go, go.
走 走 走
Hey!
不是
How could you puke on my car!
你怎么趴我车上
Xu Li.
许力
Drive me home.
送我回去
Wait a second!
不是
Zhao Fanggang,
赵方刚
get off my car!
你给我下来
Rao Jing.
饶静
I'm really sorry,
不好意思
but I can't drive you today.
我今儿送不了你了
Get off!
你给我下来
Now!
下来
Listen, I'm serious.
赵方刚我跟你说
I'll count to three.
我数三个数啊
3!
三
2!
二
Yuheng,
师哥
you had a couple shots.
你喝酒了
Let me take you home.
我送你回去吧
No, it's fine.
不用了
Usually, it's Xiaoning
平时都是小涂
who drives everyone home.
开车送大家回去
I'm really sorry,
不好意思啊
but I'm heading to another direction.
今天不太顺路
See you, Mr. Ji.
我先走了纪总
Another direction?
不顺路
Yuheng,
师哥
let's go.
那我们走吧
I thought he had excellent tastes.
还以为他眼光多高呢
That his tastes were impeccable.
审美多好呢
But it turns out, the dream girl
结果心心念念
he's been longing for all these years
这么多年的白月光
is actually someone like that.
就是这啊
Since she is so close,
既然白月光离得不远
why bother starting a relationship
当初何必找我谈什么
with the intention of marriage?
以结婚为目的的恋爱
His dream girl is taking him home.
白月光送他回家
He must be thrilled.
他应该很开心吧
I'm glad I caught up with you.
还好赶上了
Why did you come here?
你怎么来地铁站了呀
Didn't you drive?
你不是开车的吗
Where's your car?
车呢
You didn't want to drive,
你不愿意开
so I just Parked it at Juchuan.
我就停在菊川了
The parking fees there are quite steep.
那儿的停车费很贵的
Such a waste.
浪费
But that's better than you being upset.
那也总比你不开心强
You're mad at me, right?
是不是生我气了
I'm not.
我没有生你气啊
Who said I am mad?
谁说我生你气了
If he really liked Tang Yuhui,
如果他真的喜欢唐羽卉
and I just asked him directly,
那我叭叭地问
wouldn't that just be awkward?
岂不是自讨没趣
I...
我
just got my period.
来大姨妈了
Feeling a bit emotional
有点情绪
is completely normal.
也是很正常的呀
Are you in pain?
是不是肚子疼
After we get back,
一会儿回去
I'll make you some brown sugar ginger tea.
我帮你煮一碗红糖姜汤
Sure.
随便
Let me help you with that.
我帮你拿吧
No, I'm fine.
不用 我自己拿
You're clearly upset.
还说不生气
Can I ask you something?
我问你个问题呗
What type of girl did you like
你大学时期
back in college?
喜欢什么类型的女孩呀
Why the sudden curiosity?
怎么突然想要问这个了
If you don't want to answer, that's fine.
不想回答就算了
I didn't really have a specific type.
没有什么特定的类型
As long as it was her,
只要是她
I was good with it.
什么模样都行
That doesn't really tell me much.
那你这不等于没说吗
Someone who is clear-headed,
清醒仗义
cheerful and confident?
开朗自信
That sounds like
这是写在
something from a job listing.
招聘启事上的东西
Let me rephrase that.
那我重新说
The girl I like
我喜欢的女孩
has a high ponytail,
梳着高马尾
and when she smiles,
笑起来
it's bright and refreshing.
笑声很爽朗
High ponytail?
高马尾
Well,
那
a lot of girls
很多女孩子
have that.
都是
Sorry!
不好意思
It's OK.
没事 没事
It's all good.
没关系
Are you alright?
没事吧
Let me check.
别动 我看看
Just a bump.
就撞了一下
No need to make a fuss about it.
不用小题大做的
OK,
那正好
I have a question for you too.
我也问你一个问题
You mentioned earlier that artsy men
你今天说文艺男青年
are your ideal type.
是你的理想型
Is that true?
认真的吗
Just like you,
我跟你一样
as long as it's him,
只要是他
I'm good with it.
怎么都行
Xiaoning,
筱柠
I made you some ginger tea.
我给你煮了一碗红糖水
Just put it there.
你帮我放门口吧
Thanks!
谢谢
OK.
好
By the way,
对了
is your forehead OK?
额头没事吧
It's fine.
没事
Just
就
a little bump, no biggie.
碰了一下下而已
Alright.
行
If you're feeling unwell,
身体不舒服的话
just get some sleep.
早点休息
Don't stay up too late.
别熬太晚了
Drink it while it's warm.
趁热喝
Do I look good with a ponytail?
我扎马尾好看吗
When I smile,
我笑起来
is it bright and refreshing?
爽朗吗
Are you alright?
你没事儿吧
Has your account been hacked?
你是不是被盗号了
Artsy men...
文艺青年
Should I try my best
我该努力
to become your ideal type?
成为你的理想型吗
You already are.
你已经是了
Hello, this is Dairui Bank.
喂 您好代瑞银行
Regarding the loan,
想就上次贷款的事情
I'm calling for a follow-up.
跟您做个回访
If you don't have time now, that's OK.
现在没时间没关系
Once
等您
you're done,
忙完了以后
just let me know.
跟我说一下
And then I'll call you back. OK?
我给您打过去可以吗
Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
What?
干什么
That's terrible.
过分了啊
What happened?
咋了
Was it you
是不是你
who left me on
昨天晚上
the subway last night?
把我扔在地铁上
I ended up passing ten stops.
害我坐过了十个站
I've been nice to you all the time.
亏我平时对你那么好
Xu Li,
许力
that's really terrible.
过分了
Don't blame me.
不是我
Who should I blame?
那是谁
Mr. Zhao,
赵经理
now that we're on this subject,
既然说到这儿了
then I have to
那我就不得不
bring this up.
说一下啊
Yesterday, you're so persistent,
昨天您死皮赖脸地
refusing to leave
赖在我的副驾驶上
my passenger seat.
不下去
You even threw up in my car.
还吐了我一车
It cost me 200 yuan to get it cleaned.
洗车花了两百
Gimme a transfer via WeChat.
微信转给我
Thanks.
谢谢
So it was you...
原来是你啊
What an evil witch!
真够狠的
Do you realize that
你知不知道
it's quite dangerous for boys
现在男孩子在外面
out there nowadays?
也是很危险的
Boys?
男孩子
You really overestimate
您太高估
your own attractiveness.
自己的颜值了吧
You also underestimate
你也太低估
women's taste.
我们女性的审美了吧
Mr. Zhao.
赵经理
Rao Jing,
饶静
the wheel of fortune turns.
风水轮流转
You'll be
总有一天
in a tough spot because of me.
你会死在我的手上
Sure, thank you,
多谢你啊
just watch my gestures.
看手势啊
Tang Yuhui,
唐羽卉
didn't come to work today?
今天没来上班
She went to the
她早上跟领导
second phase of the Park
去园区二期
to visit a client with our boss.
拜访客户去了
Xiaoning,
小涂
you look worn out.
看你脸色这么差
You must be exhausted.
累的吧
Preparing for exams is tough,
虽然备考很辛苦
but you still need to find a balance.
但是也要劳逸结合
Make sure to freshen up after work.
下班记得补个妆
I'll take you on a blind date.
哥带你相亲去
A blind date?
相亲
I was just joking yesterday.
我昨天开玩笑呢
I not only have exams,
小赵哥我不仅要考试
but need to find clients.
我还要找客户呢
How would I find the time
哪有时间
to think about blind dates?
想着相亲的事啊
How about now?
现在想啊
I was busy reaching out
我昨天晚上
to the guy last night.
都抓紧联系了
We can't just leave him hanging, right?
总不好放人家鸽子吧
Yes, we can.
可以放
Don't feel pressured.
别有压力
I'm gonna
有你小赵哥给你镇场子
be around.
别怕
After work,
下班
make sure to freshen up.
记得补个妆
Mr. Zhao.
赵经理
Keep your distance from my apprentice.
以后离我徒弟远点
The wheel of fortune turns...
风水轮流转
A WeChat message wouldn't hurt, right?
也不知道发个微信
This guy is so unreliable.
这小子太不靠谱了
He didn't bother to tell us he'd be late.
迟到也不提前说一声
He's already five minutes late.
都迟到五分钟了
Don't be upset.
你别生气啊
When he gets here,
一会儿等他来了
I'll have a serious talk with him.
我好好说说他
I'm not angry, Mr. Zhao.
我没生气小赵哥
Is it possible
有没有可能
that he has something going on?
他有什么事
Or maybe he just doesn't want to come?
或者是不想来了
But he's too embarrassed to say it.
不好意思说呀
How about this:
要不
Let's go to another restaurant.
咱们换一家餐厅吧
I'm buying.
我请你吃
Come on,
走
let's go to another place.
咱们换一家餐厅
Oh, come on,
别呀
Xiaoning,
小涂
just ten more minutes.
咱们再等十分钟
When I was
我昨儿
talking to him on the phone yesterday,
跟他打电话的时候
he was very excited about this.
他可积极了
He must be
这会儿肯定是
busy right now,
手上有什么事
so he couldn't text me back.
抽不开手回消息
Just ten more minutes.
就十分钟
If he doesn't show up,
他要是再不来
dinner is on me.
这顿饭你赵哥请了
It's OK, Mr. Zhao,
不用 小赵哥
didn't we agree on this?
咱不是事先说好的吗
If there's something urgent,
有再急的事情
he should at least give us a heads-up.
也应该打声招呼吧
Let's go.
走吧
He just replied.
他回消息了
There was a minor accident on the road.
他说路上发生了点剐蹭
He'll definitely be here
半个小时之内
within half an hour.
一定能赶到
Mr. Ji?
纪总
Didn't he say
他不是说
he wouldn't give any special treatment?
不会特别关照吗
The good project
这有园区的好项目
has still ended up
还是落在
in the hands of his junior.
自己师妹手里了
Why are you sitting back?
怎么又坐下了
Didn't you mention
小赵哥不是说
he will be here soon?
你同学马上到吗
My date.
相亲啊
Alright, alright!
好 好 好
I'll send him a message right now,
我这就给他发信息
asking him to double time.
催他快一点
Awesome.
好
Is it still to your liking?
还合口味吗
This brown sugar rice cake
这红糖糍粑
is really something.
味儿真好
Good, huh?
好吃吧
Mr. Ji himself
这可是我们纪总
picked this restaurant.
选的餐厅
His choice
他选的
is definitely reliable.
味道肯定没错
Your've got nice taste,
纪总选的
Mr. Ji.
真不错
As long as you're happy.
张总您满意就好
The flavor is quite nice.
这味儿是可以啊
Absolutely.
是
Let me tell you,
我跟你说啊
if our deal closed today,
今天啊咱们生意谈成了
the Park
园区
would soon see a boost in income.
马上业绩增长
Mr. Ji, try this.
纪总尝尝
I'm not really a fan of sweets.
我不太爱吃甜的
Sweet, but not overwhelming.
甜而不腻
Thanks.
谢谢
You should try this.
您二位尝尝这个
This is their signature dish.
这可是他们家的招牌
This flavor is indeed impressive.
这味道确实不错
I bet Xiaoning would love it too.
估计筱柠也会喜欢
Please dig in.
多吃点啊
OK, OK.
好 好 好
Thanks.
谢谢 谢谢
It's really good.
挺好的
Have you tried this yet?
你们尝这个了吗
Excuse me.
二位先失陪一下
Alright, I'll have a bite.
好我尝尝
Hello.
您好
Can I have a brown sugar rice cake
帮我加一份红糖糍粑
to go, please?
打包
I'll pick it up when I leave.
走的时候我来取
Sure thing, sir.
好的 先生
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm not just boasting.
我可不是王婆卖瓜啊
This brother of my classmate's
我这同学弟弟
is truly impressive.
真的很优秀
In every aspect,
条件各方面的
he's on par with our boss.
跟咱领导有得一拼
He not only perfectly matches
他不仅完全符合
your ideal type of artsy man,
你的文艺青年的理想型
but most importantly,
最重要的是
he's quite chatty.
他长嘴
He'll chat you up
没事
whenever he gets the chance.
他就哄你
He'll provide you
情绪价值
with plenty of emotional support.
给你拉得满满的
If we put him out there,
要放市场上啊
who knows,
说不定
he might be more popular than our boss.
比咱纪大领导还抢手
Is that so?
是吗
Mr. Ji.
纪总啊
Hey, boss,
领导
what a coincidence!
这么巧你也在这儿啊
I'm meeting the supervisors of the Park
我约了园区二期的领导
for dinner to discuss business.
在隔壁谈事
You were saying...
你们刚刚说
I was just chatting with Xiaoning.
刚才跟小涂聊天
I got a bit carried away.
聊兴奋了
I misspoke in the excitement.
一时口不择言
Don't take those
说的那些胡话
silly words to heart.
你别往心里去啊
They weren't silly at all.
也不是胡话呀
I think Mr. Zhao has a point.
我觉得小赵哥说得对
That guy sounds pretty good.
那人听上去是不错的
Send him a WeChat message,
你给他发个微信
telling him to take his time.
让他慢点开
If he can't make it in half an hour,
半个小时到不了
I'll wait for him for an hour.
我就等他一个小时
Okie dokie.
得嘞
If you two really hit it off,
你俩要是真成了
you would have to invite me
那回头得请你小赵哥
to your wedding!
喝喜酒啊
That's a given!
那肯定的呀
About that clothing company,
那个服装企业的
have the application documents
申请文件
been revised yet?
都改好了吗
Almost done.
差不多了
I thought the deadline is next week?
我记得不是下周截止吗
You remembered wrong.
你记错了
I meant this afternoon.
我说的是下午
Not next week.
不是下周
This afternoon.
下午
The afternoon is almost over.
下午都快过了
How about this:
这样吧
I'll finish it by tomorrow
明天改完
and definitely get it to you.
一定给你
Boss,
领导
as you can see,
你也看见了
I set Xiaoning up on a blind date.
我带小涂在这儿相亲呢
Soon,
一会儿
my classmate's brother will be here.
我同学的弟弟来了
If I'm not around,
我人要是不在
they'll just
他俩
feel very awkward.
大眼瞪小眼的多尴尬啊
I need to stick around
我得留在这儿
to help them out a bit.
给他们打打配合
They won't be awkward at all.
不尴尬呀
I'm here too, right?
我不正好也在吗
When he gets here,
等会儿你的同学来了
I'll help out.
我来打配合
You?
你配合
Xiaoning,
小涂
for us sales people,
咱们干营销的
the ability to handle cold calls is vital.
陌拜能力是基础
It's just a first meeting.
不就是第一次见面吗
Just think of him as
你就把他当成
a client.
是你的客户
Communicate more,
多沟通
chat more, get familiar.
多聊天 多熟悉
You'll be just fine.
肯定没问题的
I'll send you his WeChat
我这就把他的微信
right away.
推给你啊
I'm off now.
走了
Mr. Zhao,
小赵哥
I'm just next door.
我就在隔壁
If anything comes up,
有任何事情
let me know.
随时叫我
Let me tell you both,
我跟你们俩说啊
if we close this big deal today,
今天这大活谈成了
we expect at least 200 mil in revenue.
咱们至少进账两亿
You both should go
你们俩都去
and take a week off.
先休息一礼拜啊
Good, good.
好 好 好
Thanks, boss!
谢谢老板
This time,
这次啊
we owe it to Yuhui for making the link.
多亏了羽卉的牵线啊
Are you still here?
还在吗
Did that guy come?
那人 来了吗
The dishes are quite good too.
这菜点的也特别不错
Have you tried the shrimps?
你尝那个虾了吗
Yes,
尝了
yummy.
挺好吃的
I'm going to the restroom.
我去趟卫生间
Again?
还去啊
Yuheng, you alright?
师哥你没事吧
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
怎么不回我消息呢
I didn't check my phone.
没看手机
Looks like this guy isn't reliable.
看来这人也不靠谱啊
It's been hours
迟到了这么久
and he still hasn't shown up.
也见不着他
Why even bother with this blind date?
这种相亲干吗要来
You can look out for your junior.
你可以关照师妹
Why can't I go on a blind date?
我为什么不能来相亲啊
These are irrelevant.
这能是一回事吗
There's a company in the Park.
园区二期有家企业
It's quite reputable.
非常有来头
Tang Yuhui took the initiative,
唐羽卉是主动请缨
saying she has a connection with the boss.
说她跟那个老板有交情
That's why I brought her along.
我才带上她的
Mr. Zhao also mentioned,
那小赵哥还说呢
in our line of work,
干我们这行的
networking is key.
多认识一个人多条路
That's why I came.
所以我才来的
If you need,
你要是想要路
I can help you build the future.
我可以陪着你一起铺
You don't need other people.
用不着别人
I've never expected
我可从来都没想过
to rely on you for work.
工作上要靠你啊
I'm not just talking about work here.
我说的也不只是工作
You go ahead.
你继续
You should head back now.
你赶紧回去吧
She's worried sick.
别让人家担心了
Yuheng, are you alright?
师哥 你没事吧
I noticed you didn't look well.
刚刚看你脸色不太好
Should I take you to the hospital?
要不我现在陪你去医院
It's al...
没关
Hello?
喂
I'm fine.
我没事
I'll be back shortly.
一会儿就回去了
That's good to hear.
没事就好
But, Yuheng,
可是师哥
they asked about the contract,
他们问起合同的事
and I was worried I might mess it up.
我怕答错
OK.
我知道了
I'll...
我
be right back.
现在过去
Let's talk later at home.
晚点我们回家说
I looked it up online.
我在网上查过了
During your period,
生理期
hormonal changes can happen,
会让激素发生变化
which can lead to overthinking.
容易让人胡思乱想
Just order something,
先点点吃的
and I'll take care of the bill later.
一会儿我来买单
I'll drive you home after I'm done.
等我结束来接你啊
Don't be upset.
别生气了
I'd like to order.
点菜吧
Here's the menu, miss.
女士请点餐
All done, finally.
终于弄完了
Everything alright with Xiaoning?
小涂那边还好吧
Maybe I should check on her.
要不我赶过去瞅瞅呢
Here, use this card.
来 刷这张
Here, here's a card for you.
来弟弟给你一张卡
You have one too.
来 你也有一张
It's not sufficient.
这个钱不够
That should definitely cover it.
那肯定有
Rao Jing?
饶静
Take this one as well.
这个也都给你
Take them all.
全 全都给你
Just swipe it; it should have funds.
你刷 肯定有钱
Ms. Rao.
饶经理
Wakey, wakey.
起床了
I thought you're immune to alcohol.
也有你喝多的一天啊
Sir.
先生
8,000 yuan?
花八千
How long did she drink?
她喝了多久啊
Two hours.
两个小时
She spent 8,000 in 2 hours?
两个小时花八千
Actually,
是这样的
the cards this lady used
这位女士拿出的卡呢
all show insufficient balance.
都显示余额不足了
So,
所以
I'm supposed to pay
现在这些钱
for her drinks?
要我来付
Since you two
既然你们两位
are friends,
是朋友的话
could you please...
那能不能请您
No way.
不能
Let go.
松手
You should pay.
你付钱
Let go!
松手啊
Look at that guy,
看这男的
clearly trying to avoid responsibility.
明摆着是不想负责任
What a scum!
真不够爷们
Yeah.
是啊
Obviously, he's a womanizer
一看就是始乱终弃
and trying to abandon that girl.
想把女的自己丢在这儿
Shame on him!
真够不要脸的
I shouldn't have come in.
我就不该进来
Just scan my QR.
扫吧 扫吧
Make it fast.
扫快一点
So I could feel better.
我心里还好受一些
I'm thirsty.
渴啊
Thank you.
谢谢
Give her a glass of water.
给她倒杯水
OK.
好
Give me one as well.
给我也倒杯水
Take me home.
送我回家
Your outfits are
你说你身上随随便便
all worth a fortune.
一套行头都万八千的
And,
还有
just last quarter,
上个季度
and the one before,
上上个季度
you received some juicy bonuses.
也拿了不少奖金
How come after a breakup,
怎么失个恋
you can't even afford to pay for drinks?
连喝酒的钱都付不起
You talk too much!
你怎么话这么多呀
Who broke up?
谁失恋
What breakup?
失什么恋
Yeah, sure.
你就嘴硬吧
The waiter
刚才人服务员
just told me
都跟我说了
that the one who came in with you
跟你一起来的
was a young guy.
是个年轻男孩
He went off on his own.
扔下你自己走了
That's not my boyfriend.
那又不是男朋友
Just a friend with benefits.
那就是消遣解闷的
Alright, my apologies.
失敬 失敬
I really underestimated you before.
之前我还是低估你了
Keep all the booty calls
养一池鱼
just to pass the time.
就为了解闷
Have you considered this?
那你没想想
To them,
你在人心里
you're just a source of amusement too.
也就是个解闷的
So, mutual amusement,
那相互解闷
isn't that fantastic?
不也挺好的吗
At least it keeps
最起码不孤单
loneliness at bay.
不寂寞
Zhao Fanggang.
赵方刚
I'm glad to have you around.
还好有你
You argue with me every day.
每天跟我斗嘴
That's funnier.
有趣多了
So here I am, working hard,
合着我拼死拼活地
competing with you.
在你屁股后面奋起直追
I'm merely your
我就是你一个
source of entertainment?
逗趣解闷的
That hurts!
你也太看不起人了
Zhao Fanggang,
赵方刚
I'll have you know,
我跟你说
being able to entertain me
能让我饶静消遣
is your greatest honor.
是你的福气
Yeah, sure,
我谢谢你
would you take that
这福气给你
honor if you're me?
你要不要
Last time,
上次
you left me on the subway.
你把我扔在地铁站
This time,
这次
have a taste of your own medicine.
我也不管你了
No way.
不行
No, no.
不行 不行
Come here.
你过来
I'll give you my address.
我告诉你我家的地址
Did you get that?
记住了吗
Are you really drunk or not?
你到底喝没喝醉啊
When we get home,
反正待会儿到家
you tell me.
你告诉我就行
Taxi!
出租
I look forward to working with you.
期待跟您的正式合作了
OK.
好
See you then.
那咱们改天约
Bye.
先走了
Take care.
注意安全
Yuheng,
师哥
so,
那
I'll be leaving then.
我先走了
Be safe.
路上注意安全
Sure.
行
Ji Yuheng.
纪昱恒
Am I just imagining?
我是在胡思乱想吗
But what if it is true?
可万一我想的都是真的
And what if I
而我
shatter your ideal image,
又戳破了你的白月光
your hidden feelings?
你的隐晦感情
Then how can we move forward?
那我们之后如何相处
Can we still keep this going?
我们的关系还能继续吗
You look silly when you smile.
一笑就傻乎乎的
Someone like Tang Yuhui
唐羽卉那样的
has to be Ji Yuheng's ideal type.
才是纪昱恒的理想型吧
Xiaoning!
筱柠
Door is locked.
已关锁
Good night.
晚安
I need a break.
先歇会儿
Sure.
好
You guys keep going.
你们继续
Our top A student
纪大学霸今天在球场上
is truly awesome today.
怎么这么厉害啊
Do you think maybe his crush
你们说是不是
is watching him in the audience?
有他喜欢的人在观战
His crush must be
能被他喜欢的人
someone really exceptional.
该有多优秀啊
Yuheng,
师哥
what kind of girl do you like?
你喜欢什么样的女生
Someone with a high ponytail,
高马尾
and refreshing smiles.
笑声爽朗的
High ponytail!
高马尾 高马尾
He was talking about you!
他喜欢的这不就是你吗
He's so hot!
真的很帅